question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Israel is 7 hours ahead of New York.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "The color of the pills in the Matrix were Blue and Yellow.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Ottoman Empire was created in 1299.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "As of February 2019, the &quot;Donkey Kong Country&quot; series only had released five games (not counting remakes or ports).",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The game series &quot;Titanfall&quot; runs on the Unreal Engine.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
      "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The flag of South Africa features 7 colours.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]